Episode 94
You are using
my relationship with the Bradley family to make
money.
You really disgust me.
Who's speaking?
You?
Why are you here?
Where do you think I should be?
At the hospital?
Oliver,
you pushed me down the stairs
and used my medical expenses
to threaten my daughter.
How could you
be so heartless?
How dare you say that about me,
you wicked woman!
What did you do, huh?
You betrayed
and cuckolded me.
I didn't make you pay for that.
I just
made you unconscious for two years.
You should
be grateful to me.
You're spouting nonsense.
I never
cheated on you.
Even now,
you're still blaming me for everything.
My mother has never
cheated on you.
It's all lies made up by Marcella.
She has already confessed.
She deliberately
fabricated these things.
You have never
believed in my mother.
You only believe
Marcella's words.
That's impossible.
Your mother
was indifferent to me back then.
She always went out
for no reason.
She must be seeing someone.
If I didn't go out,
where would the Curtis Group get its business from?
Enough.
He simply could not bring himself
to believe the truth.
It's useless to explain to him.
Let's go.
Wait, wait!
It's all the fault of that rebellious daughter
who lied to me.
Rhonda, for our old time's sake...
Enough.
What's the point of
saying all this now?
Oliver,
I want to divorce you
and I will sue you for
attempted murder against me two years ago.
Do you really have to go this far?